Time is a funny thing.
When I was a kid, the days lasted forever.
- One, two...
- Hide, hide, hide.
But the years...
- Three, four, five, six...
- Quick, over here.
Well, they went by so fast.
- Tim, no peeking.
- Yeah, no peeking.
- Before you know it, you're all grown up.
- Seven, eight...
- It even happened to me.
- Nine, nine and a half, ten.
Ready or not, here I come.
My name's Tim, and this,
well, this is the rest of my story.
Run for your lives.
No fair, dad. You peeked.
They call me a stay-at-home dad,
which means I hardly get to stay at home.
Buckle up, templetons.
- Ready...
- Set...
Gol
now, some might say
I still have an overactive imagination.
But being a dad is the coolestob
in the world.
It's a bunch of coolobs, really.
Sometimes I'm a race car driver.
Whoo! Daddy-o andretti!
Yay, templetons!
Well, and then sometimes
I'm the best darn cook in the county,
and I deal out every meal.
Come on, pa, hit me.
Tina.
Whoo, doggie!
And the house wins again.
Or a surgeon, if need be.
- Spork.
- Spatula.
Give my creature life.
She's alive.
We have our ups
and we have our downs.
- No, no, no. Look, lamb lamb's okay.
- Yay!
But we always stick together.
My wife, Carol.
- It's a miracle!
- She's the breadwinner of the family.
Thank you. You know what they say,
“it's all about the dough."
And I couldn't have done it
without my husband.
He really Rose to the occasion.
- It's the yeast I can do.
- Yeah, mama.
She brings home the bacon too.
While I keep an eye on our new baby Tina.
But sometimes, feels like
she's keeping an eye on me.
- And Tabitha, our little second-grader...
- Thank you.
Whoust got accepted
into the best school in town.
- Yay! Tabitha!
- We're so proud.
I still keep in touch
with the old gang foo.
Believe it or not,imbo is mayor now.
Cookie.
Of course, his wife, staci,
is the real brains behind the operation.
- Yo,imbo!
- Now, the triplets...
Busted.
Yeah, they haven't changed much.
And as for my baby brother, Ted, well,
he grew up fo be the boss, all right.
He's so busy we hardly see him anymore.
But, hey, he always remembers to send
inappropriately lavish gifts
on special occasions.
OMG! Uncle Ted is the best!
All in all,
my life is pretty perfect.
But all that was about fo change.
Good heavens! I'll save you!
Hal -
thanks, babe.
Stay calm, Tabitha.
I'm coming for you.
I'm gonna save you from the bubbling lava.
Dad, what are you doing?
Ew, gross. It went everywhere.
Come on,
this is the candy volcano of doom.
You used to love it.
But I'm trying to do my homework,
or I'm doomed.
Oh.
Because if there's one thing
I've learned, you're only a kid once.
Once you grow up, you can never go back.
Alalalalala.
Eeh.
Oh, no.
Good night, Dr. Hawking.
Carbon, boron, beryllium,
lithium, helium, hydrogen.
Nailed it.
Boom shakalaka.
"Carry the four." Gosh.
Hey there, Tabitha.
It's the good night show.
Live from your bedroom,
starring dad and mom.
And special guest, baby Tina.
Good night, little Tina.
Come back here, you.
Good night, mom.
Good night, sweetheart.
Mama's gonna kiss you.
» good night song with your dad
what?
It's time for your good night song.
Oh, no, thanks.
I'm listening to white noise!
Helps me fall asleep!
Shh. Shh.
Hey, what would you say to me helping you
rehearse for the holiday pageant?
Yes! Right?
I can come to school with you
and you can get all your friends together.
And we can rehearse together,
go get some ice cream after. My treat.
No! You can't do that.
Um, liability issues.
It's this whole thing.
Oh. Right, right. Right.
Whoa. How about your favorite
bedtime story?
You know, the one about...
Uncle Ted was a magical talking baby.
There was a rocket full of puppies
and you saved the world.
It was a good story, wasn't it?
Well, it didn't really make
a lot of sense.
Theokes were good, right?
Mmm.
Okay. Um...
Dad.
My schedule is brutal tomorrow.
Yeah. My schedule's pretty brutal too.
Oh, don't forget lamb lamb.
Good night, lamb lamb.
Good night, uncle Ted.
I hope to grow up and be a success,
just like you.
Maybe we'll see you soon.
Good night, Tabitha.
Don't you think
I'm a little old for that now?
Okay.
I think it's time we both grow up.
I look forward to greeting you
at the breakfast table.
Sweet dreams.
Mmm.
Where has the time gone?
How should I know?
Wait, wait. I see light.
Out of my way.
At long last.
The sweet breath of freedom.
Wizzie?
You there, what century is this?
Unhand me, vile ogre.
No. Wizzie, it's me. It's Tim.
Is it really you?
Come closer. Let me see your face.
Closer.
Closer still.
Oh, Timothy. It is you!
You cast me into eternal darkness
and wreaked havoc on my circadian rhythms.
I'm sorry, wizzie.
Hey, but you look great though.
Except for the arm, you mean.
- Didn't even notice.
- You thought it!
I mean, I noticed it, 'cause...
You obviously don't have an arm. I...
You would never
treat lamb lamb this way.
Well, I gave her to my daughter. Tabitha.
You have produced an heir, Timothy?
- Two, actually.
- Two! Let the bells ring!
No. Wizzie, stop.
Wizzie. Be quiet.
Yes. Yes! It's a time for celebration!
No. It's not the time for celebration.
“What? What is it?
- Be quiet.
- What is it, Tim?
I don't know. I guess I'must not feeling
very celebratory right now.
Oh?
Tabitha.
Man, wizzie, she's growing up so fast.
It's like she doesn't even
need me anymore.
Yes, first they start spending
less time with you.
Mmm.
Then they stop coming to you for advice.
Exactly.
Soon they take you for granted.
I guess.
Then break your arm. “What?
Then stuff you into a box!
Okay. Wizzie, you're not helping.
Okay. I'must... I'm afraid Tabitha and I
are growing apart.
Like... like I did with my brother.
Oh.
I thought we had
all the time in the world.
But you can't turn back time, can you?
How dare you question my power!
- Turn back, turn back.
- Oh, here we go.
Oh, great wheel of li...
Wait.
Did you hear that?
Ugh! Never abuse the snooze button!
Shh!
It sounds like it's coming
from the baby's room.
What is it?
A creature of the night? Witches?
- Is it the baying of the hounds of hell?
- Wizziel
don't go, Tim!
I can turn back time.
To the golden years,
when it wasust you and me.
My good arm.
Don't open the door. Remember last time!
If you would like to make a call,
please hang up and try again.
If you need help, hang up
and then dial your operator. Thank you.
Hello?
If you would like to make a call,
please hang up and try again.
Anh! It'sust my phone.
Get it together, man.
Oh, Tina, you little klepto...
- Nighty-night.
- Maniac!
Whoal
hi, daddy.
Tabitha? Is that you?
Whoal
you should've seen your face.
Oh, it's priceless.
You're... do you... you... did you...
You... you can talk?
Yep.
- I'm in the family business.
- It's a clip-on tie.
You see, daddy,
babycorp is more of what I...
Whoops.
Daddy, daddy, come in.
Can you hear me? Daddy?
Do you read me?
How many fingers am I holding up?
Thursday?
Ah!
Wait, wait. You're from babycorp?
Yes! Babycorp is more of what I call
a side hustle for me.
Uh-huh.
The point is I'm all in on the templetons.
Go templetons!
- Okay.
- You guys really know how to baby a baby.
I mean, it's incredible.
Not that's it's all five-star.
- You got a lot of issues.
- Sure. Yeah.
- We'll talk about that later.
- Oh, my gosh! I can't believe this.
Hey! Wanna go scare the crap outta mom?
Daddy, please stay focused.
Oh. Right, right, right.
There's a crisis at babycorp.
What is it this time? Kittens?
No. This time it's even worse.
Worse than kittens? Yes!
That's why I volunteered
for this supersecret assignment.
Whoo! I wanna help.
What do you want me to do?
That's the spirit, daddy.
You are exactly who I need.
- Yes!
- To get uncle Ted.
No. What?
What's with the face?
Daddy, babycorp can't wait any longer.
All the pressure's on me, pop.
When I volunteered for this gig,
I thought it would be easy.
But you two never see each other.
It's so sad.
It's like, "f-minus, see me after class."
Sad? Yeah, maybe. A little. I don't know.
Did you forget to call him?
I noticed you can be
a little absentminded.
Sorry, what?
It'sust that you tend to procrastinate.
You have to get him here for the holidays.
No, I'm not gonna
call him right now. No.
Daddy, can't never could.
- Did you two have a fight or something?
- No.
- But you're mad at him?
- Stop that! It's complicated.
Why"? Do you need help using your phone?
No. I don't need help using my...
Okay. What's the problem?
What's the issue? Talk to me.
There's no point, okay?
I call him, I invite him.
He never shows up.
He's always got a work meeting
or a business trip or a conference call.
All he cares about is work.
But after a while youust stop trying.
He's still your brother.
You were partners.
Yeah, I guess sometimes youust...
You grow up and grow apart.
Daddy. Don't say no.
What if everybody said no?
Nothing would happen.
Nothing would get off the ground.
You gotta wake up every day
and you gotta say, "yes, yes, yes!"
Surprise me. Say yes.
This is really disappointing.
And now I'm getting mad!
It's late.
We can work on this tomorrow, okay?
Oh!
Whoopsie. Your little horsey fell off.
Another day won't hurt, right?
Good night, sweetie.
Hmm.
Horsey fell off...
Tabitha?
Huh?
Uh, don't worry. I got it.
Where is she?
“Where's who? What?
- I came as fast as I could.
- Ted?
- I canceled all my meetings.
- What are you doing here?
Why are you yelling?
Where's Tabitha?
Tabitha? Where is she?
- Ted.
- Uncle Ted!
You're here! You're really here!
Which arm is it? Left or right?
Is it your fibula? Talk to me.
Good dilation. Open up. Say, "aah."
- Are you okay? You look okay.
- What are you doing?
Don't worry. I'm fine, uncle Ted.
- That's my girl.
- Whoo-hoo.
Uh, what brings you into town?
- Well, Tabitha fell off her pony.
- She did?
- I did?
Tim left me a voice mail.
- He did?
- I did?
You did.
Hello, this is your brother. Help.
Tabitha fell off horsey.
Good night, sweetie.
Well, that was unsettling.
I swear I didn't leave that message.
On purpose. I...
Butt-dialed?
With my butt...
While I was talking in my sleep.
I do that sometimes.
You sleep butt-dialed me?
With my butt.
I knew there must be
a perfectly logical explanation.
- And there it is.
- Hmm.
- All that matters is that you're here.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yay.
- Absolutely... uh, for now.
Uncle Ted, please stay
for Christmas. Please.
Sorry, sweetie.
I can't do Christmas on the 25th.
But, uncle Ted, I missed you so much.
I missed you so much.
Don't you think
I'm a little old for that now?
Can I talk to you in the kitchen?
Alone.
The baby, Tim?
She's been sent from up there.
- Upstairs?
- That's right.
Babycorp.
So, you're saying the voice mall
was some kind of call for help.
Yes! No.
She comes
from a secret corporation run by babies.
Tim, I'm gonna give you
the name of a doctor.
Roy federman.
Just tell him I sent you. Okay?
What are they saying?
We should give them some privacy.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thanks.
I'm not crazy!
Youust don't remember. Tell him, Tina.
- He...
- She can't talk, Tim.
Fee - stop interrupting!
Interrupting what? I don't hear anything.
Except your obnoxious voice,
you hear that.
I have a beautiful voice.
Fine. I can prove
that everything I'm saying is real.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
Suck it, Ted.
I beg your pardon?
You. Suck.
No, no, Tim. You suck.
- Time to go buy a Christmas tree.
- But we already have a Christmas tree.
- No, we don't. No, we don't.
- Yes, we do. Yes, we do.
- Suck it, suck it, suck it.
- Get that pacie outta my face.
Excuse me. I hate to interrupt.
But may I make a suggestion?
Why don't you both suck it?
- She can talk.
- A lot.
Buckle up, boys.
Baby on board!
That's what I'm talking about.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo!
Ah.
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
Wow.
I'm home.
Yeah. See? It's all real.
Whoa.
Is that me?
If you're fishing for a compliment,
ya caught one!
You are a legend in thisoint.
A statue?
Well, I did single-handedly
save the company.
Double-handedly. Right?
We were partners.
Really? I don't see your statue.
I still love you, daddy.
They got the head size right.
Take it from me, you have
to be aggressive if you wanna get ahead.
Climb that corporate ladder
until you're the last baby
standing at the top.
Actually, I prioritize
a good work-life balance
and a positive environment
where my ideas are valued.
Oh, you're serious.
You're funny, uncle Ted.
I wonder why they didn't mention that
in your file?
My file?
- You saw my file?
- Yep.
- What does it say?
- It says a lot.
This is the crisis center.
Whoa. Wow.
This is where we monitor all threats
to babies around the world and Hawaii.
This is so cool. This is so cool.
"I'm Godzilla."
"Run for your lives."
- Why did we bring him?
- Daddy, get down from there.
We can play on it later
when no one is looking.
What's the crisis?
Yeah! Here we go.
What's the crisis, sweetie?
Rusty, roll it.
Huh?
He's new.
Just imagine baby surgeons.
Uh-oh.
Or baby astronauts.
Floaly, floaty, float.
Yes, babies are gonna run the world
one aay.
And that day is coming
sooner than you think.
Hello. My name is Dr. erwin Armstrong,
founder of the acorn center
for advanced childhood.
Wait a minute,
that's Tabitha's school.
Here at the center,
we believe babies
are the ultimate learning machines.
Isn't that right, little Nathan?
- Yeah!
- Okay.
They should use their precious time
fo develop faster, push harder.
- Mmm.
- Ugh.
Parents, they have the best intentions,
of course, but they're not experts.
After all, the only thing
holding your child back is... you.
You!
This explains why
Tabitha's been pulling away from me.
- It's the school.
- Everybody, wave.
- "Bye, mommy. Bye, daddy. Sayonara!”
- Bye, mommy. Bye, daddy.
Now, in the past six months,
these schools have been popping up
all over the world.
Uh, so what's the problem?
The school is the problem.
Yeah. School is evil.
No, daddy, not all schools are evil.
- It'sust this one. Okay?
- Okay.
If Armstrong's philosophy keeps spreading,
it could be the end of childhood.
Nol!
Childhood was
the worst three years of my life.
Huh? “Aw.
But luckily, you get a do-over.
A second chance.
Babycorp has developed
a new super-duper baby formula
that can turn a grown-up back into a baby.
We have it in cherry, grape,
orange and lime.
- For real?
- Wait, wait, wait.
You want me to be a baby?
Hey, it's what you do best.
So you can infiltrate the school
and find out
what Dr. Armstrong is really up to.
Babycorp will take care of the rest.
Whoo!
Oh!
It's the perfect disguise.
And it only lasts 48 teensy-weensy hours.
Oh, I am in on the mission.
Sorry, pops. It's not your mission.
"Warning: May cause drooling, babbling,
emotional outbursts, fits of laughter,
loss of bowel control, chubby thighs."
I think some guys at my gym
take this stuff.
My texting hand!
Even though it is your daughter's school.
Doesn't seem fair, does it?
Daddy, no. Please stop.
Whoa!
What? It actually worked!
It's mine!
- I'm better with this kind of thing.
- Oh!
And what kind of thing is that,
flock of seagulls?
- Everything!
- Gotchal
you might feel very emotional,
have some mood swings.
Oh!
Hey!
Ouch! There's the awkward stage.
Now, the tea's hot, Connie.
You always have to be the hero,
don't you?
What's that supposed to mean?
Never see him!
All of a sudden, he shows up with a pony.
You'reustealous, helmet head.
She's my daughter!
She's my niece.
Do you want cream or sugar?
I was always the successful one.
Mommy says no running in the house!
Mmm.
Hand over the bottle, mullet.
You can't hug money, you know.
Ooh!
But you can, Tim. You can!
Men. Am I right?
It's not personal.
It's business, Leslie.
Well, it's personal to me,
Lindsey.
Stop, stop, stop!
I'm sorry, Connie.
I have to cut this short.
Tomorrow we'll talk about your problems.
Okay! Time-out! This has gone far enough!
Hey! We're home.
- And we got another tree.
- A real one!
Upstairs now. Go, go, go!
Push it. No, no. Pull it.
- Go, go, go!
- Push it up.
Push it. Pull it.
No. Okay. To the right.
How come I have the heavy end?
Because you're young
and strong, honey.
- Little bit more.
- Me first!
- Come on.
- Get off!
- Tim? Ted?
- Mom.
Get the cord. Get the cord!
Youust can't disappear.
You need a cover story.
- Oh, right.
- Ow! My soft spot.
Where are you guys?
Tell her you're packing.
We're upstairs... uh, packing.
- Packing? For what?
- Whoa.
Ooh. You're going
on a brother-bonding trip.
We're going on a brother-bonding trip.
Now?
But, Tim,
your parents are coming tomorrow.
They can help out.
Yeah, they could help out.
What... no, you can't leave me alone
with your parents.
Oh, Tina!
What are you doing?
All right, you know what?
You're going to babyail.
- No, no, no!
- Tabitha!
- I'm sorry.
- A little help here.
Hold it up. Come on.
This is Ted Templeton, a man.
You can go ahead and take off.
I have urgent family business.
Yes, I have a family.
Tim, I'm coming up there.
Yeah, we need to talk.
Hey, mom...
Oh! Tina!
Put that down. Put that down.
- Put that down!
- Tina!
Oh! Put that down!
Get back here. Tina, stop!
What has gotten into you?
Time for us to go!
What... now?
Yeah, my helicopter's double-parked.
- Bye!
- Wait, wait!
- So soon?
- Oh, no.
What... did they reallyust leave?
Yep.
Hide!
I gotta lose this baby fat.
Tina! What is your problem?
Now, you're gonna wake up tomorrow
and be good, Tina.
No more devil baby. Deal?
Okay.
Ew.
Thanks so much for coming in, ladies.
Would you like some fruit?
Mmm. Ow.
- What was... hey!
- Can we get on with this?
Oh.
I miss my teeth.
I've decided who's going on the mission.
Thank you. I accept.
Both of you.
Ey saa eee es
babycorp wants to get the team
back together, huh?
No. They think that's a terrible idea.
Of course they do.
Well, I'm the boss, applesauce.
And I think you two are better together
than you are apart.
Well, I work alone.
Or at least, not with him.
Hey. There's no "I" in "team."
Actually, there's no "u" in "team" either,
but there is an "m" "e."
- T-e-a-m-e?
- But teamwork doesn't seem work.
Ah! If you want something done right,
do it yourself.
We're all in it together!
Every man for himself.
One is the loneliest number.
- The ayes have it!
- We the people!
Ahal
ooh. So sorry. Okay. Good night.
Ooh.
Guess we'llust have to melt down
your big old statue
and turn it into participation trophies.
Please, no. Don't hurt my statue!
Now... we have secret intel
that Dr. Armstrong leaves his office
every morning at 11:15.
You need to sneak in there,
plant these surveillance devices,
and report back to me.
Oh, man. This is so cool.
Testing.
strangers in the night
now, I've arranged for a school bus
to be here at 8:00 A.M. sharp!
- Thank you, Connie.
- Nighty-night.
Do not be late.
Got it.
Easy-breezy-taco-peasy, boys.
Let's get some sleep.
Hey, what's the matter?
It's nothing.
Oh, sweetie, don't worry.
I'm sure your dad will be back in time
to see you in the pageant.
That's okay.
What? Don't you want him to come?
- I guess.
- Of course you do.
Now go back to sleep.
Good night, mom.
Good night, sweetie.
- Don't you want him to come?
- / guess.
Don't you think
I'm a little old for that now?
I think it's time we both grow up.
The trial of Timothy Leslie Templeton
is now in session.
- Ha! Leslie.
- Trial?
Wait, what are the charges?
Fraud!
Claiming to be the world's best dad.
- But I never said...
- Exhibit a!
Come on. That was a gift.
I suggest you let your attorney
do the talking.
Oh, no!
Back in my day,
you had to earn one of these babies.
Dad, what? I did not...
His best friend was an alarm clock.
Mom.
He broke my arm.
No, I didn't! It was my brother.
Objection, your honor.
Sustained.
We theury find the defendant...
- A failure.
- Tabitha!
Will you please help me out?
Whoa! Dad, the homework,
it'sust too much.
Tabithal
time's up.
- Wait. No!
- Save me, daddy. Save me!
Oh, man. That was crazy.
We overslept! We overslept?
- Wake up, little halflings!
- We overslept.
Wake up! What year is it?
Oh, no.
This is bad. No. No!
Get up. Get up. We gotta go!
Come on. We're gonna be late for...
I'm gonna email it to you.
What's going on?
I forgot to set wizzie
for daylight savings!
- What?
- Daylight can't be saved, Tim.
Oh, I gotta get the plant
and the bug we gotta plant.
- Grab whatever. We gotta go.
- Do not panic!
- Godspeed, boys.
- Let's roll.
Upsies. I need upsies!
Get dressed.
What have you done to me?
No, really”? What? Are we going sailing?
Oh, no. No, no. It's leaving.
Wait, no, no. Stop! Stop! Come back!
Ahoy! Come back!
Great, Matey. What are we gonna do now?
Oh, no!
Precious, my noble steed.
We must not be late
for our first day of school.
Oh. Gross.
Huh?
Tally-ho, precious!
This pony hates me.
It's not that she hates you, Tim.
Sheust doesn't respect you.
Go left. Go left!
I'm gonna go where navigation says.
- Zurn left.
- Thank you, navigation.
7urn right.
- Sorry!
- Turn left proceed on the current route.
Yee-haw!
Recalculating.
Hold onto your holster. Yah!
Oh, no. It's Carol.
- Don't answer it!
- Hi.
Tim, how's your bonding trip?
Uh...
Whoa, slow down!
How is your...
Bonding trip?
- You're here.
- Oh, no.
I mean, I wish you were here.
Aw, we miss you too. Don't we, girls?
- We're, uh...
- We're rebooting our relationship.
And restoring the closeness
that we once felt.
- That's so great.
- We've gofta go.
Where are you?
- Uh, a hockey game.
- He shoots, he scores!
He scores!
Ladies and gentlemen, he scores!
Busted => busted
d> busted b>
is that the police?
Uh, no, not the police.
It's a hockey alarm.
Faster, Tim.
I ain't going back to the clink.
Iust wanted to remind you
that Tabitha's pageant is tomorrow night.
You have to be there.
Uh, I will be there
in one shape or another.
- You promise?
- I promise.
And what about Ted?
Happy holidays, coppers.
You're never gonna take me alive, see!
Uh, he's busy.
What are you doing? It's the cops.
Sorry, officers!
Santa's got something for everybody.
Sorry!
Recalculating.
Oh, my gosh! It's so real!
It's so real! It's so real!
Tim?
Recalculating.
- Left, left!
- Recalculating.
- Right, right, right!
And now the moment we've all waited for.
Proceed on the current route.
See, Tim. Always trust... holy...
- 7im!
- Uh, Carol.
You're breaking up. I'm losing you.
- No, I can hear you fine.
- See you at the pageant!
- Golla go, bye!
- Okay.
- I whoa!
- Sorry!
Oh, no, no, no!
It's too real. It's too real!
I don't like it!
Tally-ho, precious!
No, no, no!
Tally-whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Tina!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
Tree!
You've arrived
at your destination.
Oh. Ha.
I'll send them a check.
That was fun!
You did it.
We did it.
I guess we did.
I was talking about me and precious.
- Oh.
- Isn't that right, baby?
Yeah. Right.
Get down!
Whoa. This place even looks evil.
It'sust a school.
You're overreacting, and so is babycorp.
No. I'm telling you.
This school is stressing Tabitha out.
Tabitha can handle it.
She's a real chip off the old block.
Wait, who's the block?
- I'm the block.
- You can't be the block.
- Then start acting like a block.
What does that mean?
I'm the block. I've always been the block.
Yeah, not even close.
All I do is block.
I wake up in the morning, I block.
I go to sleep, blocking. I'm the block.
Tim, enough.
- I'm the block.
- No, you're not! Stop it!
Shh.
- Sweet.
- Suckers.
Children only beyond this point.
Hey.
No crying is permitted
in the separation zone.
Looks like we gotta split up.
Good. I could use a break.
- Bye, mom!
- All right, bye, honey.
Ah! There's Tabitha.
- I'll see you after school.
- Okay.
Apparently, there's no "a"
in teamwork either.
All right, let's boogie.
Not so fast.
I'm blue. You're yellow.
You're over there
in the choo-choo.
Aw. It's full of babies.
Is it? I didn't notice.
Just kidding. It's hilarious.
Uh, wait. Your tie's crooked.
Okay, Tim, focus.
We'll meet outside Armstrong's office
at 11:15.
We'll sneak in and we'll plant the bugs.
Are you focused? Hey, what the...
Oh, I am focused, all right.
No, no. I'm not yellow. I'm blue.
11:30. Stick to the plan.
11:15!
Fifteen. Got it. The block is focused.
I'm blue!
Don't you understand? I'm blue!
Welcome, children.
Willkommen. Bienvenue.
Annyeonghaseyo and buenos dias.
Thank you for choosing fo be excellent.
Please don't touch me!
This is some ridiculous mistake!
I'm blue! I'm blue!
the wheels on the bus go pi-r-squared
circumference all around yes!
Hello.
Uh, hello. Nice plant.
This is my emotional support plant.
Hi. I'm new here.
Said nihonium to the other elements
in the periodic table.
I ooh.
Okay.
Can't sit here, or here, or there.
Seating position is determined
by class rank.
We can't possibly include your data,
given that the rigor
of your previous school
is an unknown variable.
Ooh.
Sick burn, Nathan!
Ow.
Here. You can take my seat.
I'm so proud of you.
I mean, thanks.
Okay.
Good morning.
Good morning, Dr. Armstrong.
- Very warm welcome. Thank you.
- Huh?
As you can see, we've got a new colleague
joining us foday.
- Whoo.
- Hello.
New colleague,
why don't you introduce yourself?
Uh, my name's ti... um, Marcos.
- Mmm.
- Marcos lightspeed.
Marcos lightspeed.
Yeah, colorful, characterful,
and I like it
in any case,
welcome, Marcos, to blue unit.
Our most advanced class.
Ooh, this is rarefied air we're breathing.
Here at the acorn center,
we believe that all competition is...
I'm trapped in the dum-dum holding tank.
I'm having a panic attack!
There must be a way out of here.
Something doesn't smell right.
Blueberry.
I have to get out of here.
Hi.
Don't look at me.
Okay.
And our first subject today is...
No fractions, no fractions. Whoa.
Particle physics.
Yes! What?
Yes!
Who knows which scientist first theorized
that the universe has a limit beyond which
the laws of physics break down?
- Oh! Me, me, me!
- Wow. Everybody seems to know.
Senor lightspeed.
Um, Dr. flambaisley...
Oh, that's the wrong answer.
His brain sure doesn't move
at light speed.
- Okay. Anybody else?
- I know, right?
Right here.
Max planck.
That's correct.
Tabitha has sel the bar.
First one on the board.
Ding-ding-ding. Way to go, Tabitha.
You're going down, Templeton.
Bring it on, Nathan.
Yeah, Tabitha. Get him.
Next subject.
Ancient Greek.
Opa!
Uh, Oprah!
Attention! Attention, everyone.
Who wants to play Shawshank?
No! What?
Who wants to go outside and play?
Does that sound fun? Good.
Now, anybody have any ideas?
No!
Come on, people.
We need to think outside the box.
- Me, me!
- You, Bo peep.
We can build a hot-air balloon
out of Popsicle sticks and bubble gum.
And how would it fly?
Pixie dust!
Get back in the box, Bo peep.
- All the way in?
- All the way in.
- Yay!
- Can we get in the box, too?
- Can we?
- Glue.
I like glue.
Who doesn't?
But we're trying to brainstorm here.
Glue's good.
Think, think, think, think.
Think, think, think, think, think, think.
Bingo!
Next subject.
X is equal to the derivative of...
Ooh, me! Itself.
Kudos for Tabitha.
Wow. You knew that?
The world's leading producer
of bauxite is...
Oh! Australia.
Once again, Tabitha's on the board.
- Very good.
- Yes, Tabitha!
We've got 15 minutes, people.
The difference in try and triumph
isust a little oomph.
Oomph!
Go big or go home.
Okay. Going home.
- Let's pick up the pace.
- No!
Hands down, Norma rae. This is my time.
To be, or not to be? Tabitha?
- To be.
- That's correct
can anyone tell me the horsepower
of a 302 engine?
Uh, seven?
Oh, boy.
Weak sauce, Nathan. That was weak.
Tabitha, have an idea about that?
300 horsepower with a four-barrel carb.
Wow.
Her dad must be a genius.
On my signal, unleash heck.
Fire!
Yes!
I found a cure!
Yes! Yes! She did it! She did it!
Marcos!
I did it. I did it.
Remember, your size
doesn't determine your strength.
Well, so far its Tabitha number one
and everybody else last.
No!
Psst. Hey, Tabitha. You're really...
A geek. I know.
No. You're amazing.
Oh. Thanks, Marcos.
You'll be singing a different tune
at rehearsal!
The wrong tune.
You're so funny. Hilarious!
And yeah, Templeton. Don't be late.
Late. I'm late.
Next subject.
Yes.
Just a little further.
Gluel
ah!
- Excuse me.
- Yes, Marcos.
Can I have a hall pass? I have to go.
Voila. Feel free.
Now what?
Gluel
glue is bad!
Glue.
Glue is good.
How to get to the principal's office.
Of course!
You get sent to the principal's office.
Booyah!
[think it's very vital
to rock a rhyme...
here we go
it's tricky to rock a rhyme»
to rock a rhyme that's right on time»
it's tricky
it's tricky, tricky, tricky, tricky
it's tricky to rock a rhyme»
to rock a rhyme that's right on time
its tricky...
what's up, y'all?
School is...
Stupid.
Listen, you know,
I acknowledge your anger.
It's very feisty, but please sit down.
Okay.
Uh, no.
Sitting is stupid.
He's such a bad boy.
it's tricky to rock a rhyme»
to rock a rhyme that's right on time
it's tricky
- how is it, d? >
- D it's tricky
all ight. I'm afraid
you can't disrupt class any longer.
Oh, no.
Are we gonna have a talk in your office?
No.
You are gonna have a time-out.
- He's going in the box.
- The box?
No. The box makes you crazy.
The box?
sail away, sail away, sail away
start over, Marcos.
Your time-out begins now.
Relax.
Wait!
Don't cry. There, there.
All better.
It's like they always say.
If you want something done right,
you have to do it without your brother.
We meet again, doorknob.
Hello. Welcome, welcome.
Please, come in. Enitrez-vous.
- You're here.
- Oh, yes.
I... I was expecting you.
L...
I expected that you...
Would be... expecting me.
So there.
Oh, and by the way,
I know why you're here.
So... so there.
You do?
Mm-hmm. Yes, I do.
- Have a seat, please.
- Thank you.
You know what you are? Mmm?
You are, if I may, extremely intelligent.
Go on.
As a matter of fact,
I've been observing you.
Spends time wisely, check.
Makes good use
of classroom materials, check.
Keeps hands to self, check.
Hey, forget "works well with others."
You make others work well for you.
That's literally the title
of the book I'm working on.
No kidding.
You had no business being
in yellow level, did you?
It was sabotage.
Sabotage, exactly.ealousy, fear...
Hey, I faced the same obstacles.
In fact, you remind me a lot of myself
when I was your age,
which is... now.
What?
Surprise. Surprise.
What the frittata?
Well put.
He's a b... you're a baby.
I repeat, you're a baby.
So surprised you said it twice.
Unfortunately, people are not ready
for a baby in a position of power... yet.
Remind me to get the number
of your mutton chop guy.
You know, I could use somebody like you.
With a superior intelligence, like my own.
- Uh...
- Mmm.
- Really?
- Somebody who can, uh...
Mmm.
Mmm. Yeah.
Truly comprehend
what I'm trying to accomplish.
Well, you're looking at him.
Bingo. Mmm.
We have a secret level.
For very special babies.
Mmm. The best of the best. Ah, the elite.
Beyond blue?
Oh, yeah. Way beyond.
Way beyond.
There's a meeting today after school.
Babies only.
We may be small,
but we're about to teach grown-ups
a big lesson.
Lolly?
Okay.
Oh. Time for recess.
Bye, bye.
Sayonara.
Well, I think that went well.
- You're a baby.
- What?
I repeat, you're a baby.
Is he talking to me?
He better not be talking to me,
because I'll... Armstrong?
You're right, Connie.
He's talking about Armstrong.
I don't know what has gotten into her...
But she's acting strange, Dr. federman.
Isn't it a bit early for terrible twos?
Is there terrible ones?
- Is that a thing?
- Oh, piano playing bunny, you slay me.
Okey dokey.
We need some eyes on the prize,
visual confirmation here.
Oh, daddy!
If I were there I'd pinch you so hard.
sail away, sail away...
your time-out has concluded.
Sail a... sail away! What time is it?
It is time for recess.
I'm late. I'm late.
I mean, come on.
He'll understand, right?
Okay. Where is he? Where is he?
- Umph! Yeah, baby!
- No. Not my bows.
But they're not your bows...
Dnymore.
Yep, where there's crying,
there's my brother.
- Psst.
- Here you go.
Cool.
Glue. Glue. Glue.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, blue. Where do you think
youse going?
- You lost?
- Could you let me through, please?
- No!
- So what?
Did you flunk coloring class, kid?
Really, guy?
Mmm. Cherry.
Go on. Blues on the other side.
- Let him through.
- Okay, he's cool.
See. I'm cool. I'm cool.
You failed me, Tim.
I was desperate. I crawled.
I did things with glue
that I'm not proud of,
but I made it.
I made it all the way
to Armstrong's office
and then... where's Tim?
I know, I... where's Tim?
- I tried to...
- Where's Tim?
I was in the box, okay!
The box?
Glue.
Yeah, that's right.
- The box!
- The box.
Show a little respect.
See, Tim, this is why I work alone.
I'll succeed in the mission.
You can take the pony home.
The only thing you're ever gonna
succeed at is being alone.
- Fine.
- Fine!
Finel
- I like ponies.
- Ah!
Thank you for sharing.
You're blowing it, Templeton!
Yeah, Templeton!
I'm trying.
Ugh!
You always come in a beat late.
I'm sorry, Nathan. I'm doing my best.
Your best is gonna keep me out
of going touilliard.
- Yeah, Templeton!
- It's one, two, three,
- and one, two, three.
- And one, two, three.
- And one, two...
- Oh, come on!
Are you kidding me?
Iust can't do it right now, okay?
I can't. Iust can't.
- I'll do it tomorrow.
- Seriously?
All right. All right. All right.
See you at the pageant tomorrow.
Beat it.
Oh, Nathan, Nathan, let me do it.
Let me do it, Nathan.
I wanna sing the song.
No. I wanna see her fail.
Oh. Pure genius.
I can't wait.
We'll see about that.
Goodbye, children. Sayonara.
Auf wiedersehen. Adieu.
Adios, ninos.
Oh, come on!
Ah!
Oh, my gosh!
Stop what you're doing.
I see a baby pony.
I like ponies.
Over there! So cute!
That's it? No "hello"?
Not even a "hi, mom"? “What?
Hi, Tabitha!
Oh.
Hi.
What? You never told me
you had an older sister who could drive.
Uh... that's my mom.
Tabitha, don't interrupt.
I'm a new friend of Tabitha's...
Hey, stop.
Oh, really?
- I mean, weust met.
- What's your name, new friend?
Stop. You're embarrassing me.
Marcos. Marcos lightspeed.
- Ow!
- Tinal
what is with you?
Cute kid.
Well, I better get going if I'm gonna walk
those three and a half miles home.
In the show.
Without aacket.
Three and a half miles?
Three and a half, six, somewhere in there.
Yeah, well, that TV dinner
is not gonna microwave itself.
- TV dinner?
- Yeah. I'm a latchkey kid,
so I eat whatever I want,
and cartoons are my babysitter.
- No!
- Oh, yeah.
strangers in the night
exchanging glances»
jd lovers...
what is this?
Some kind of prank?
Children can be so cruel.
Hello?
Whoa! This is exactly
like Bill Gates' rec room,
but a little smaller.
What is all this?
Research and development?
Product testing?
Huh. Something tells me
this isn't day care.
Boy, could I use a spy camera
right about now.
Anyway...
Aw...
Now, aren't you a cutie
in that little karate outfit.
Huh.
Is this some kind of a ninja boy band?
Whoal
whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh!
Whoa!
I give up!
Cobra kail
sayonara, baby!
- Hey, there you are.
- Oh, hello.
Thank you.
I see that you've angered my baby ninjas.
Oh, boy. Shoo! Shoo!
What maniacal underground fortress
doesn't have ninjas, am I right?
Impressive, huh? Pretty impressive.
What do you think?
I know tuition's pretty steep,
but how do you afford all this?
Oh, that's a good question.
I taught babies to code.
- No!
- Yes, you know what they say
about having an infinite amount of monkeys
banging on typewriters.
They will eventually write Shakespeare.
A-plus. Oh, boy. You are smart.
Or the most popular apps
that money can buy.
Apps. They're writing apps.
Cat chat, palm doodle,
oh, find my nose, stock crush.
You did stock crush?
I love stock crush.
All us.
But my next app,
ooh, it's gonna change the world.
Forever.
So why bother with a school?
You could go public and make millions.
Oh!
- Billions.
Yeah, but some things
are more important than money.
Please don't say "love."
Mmm. Power.
That's more like it.
Wow. This is so amazing.
First the ride,
and now a full sit-down dinner.
Wow. What a palace!
I mean, you have electricity?
Well, yeah.
Man, you guys are beyond generous.
You're welcome anytime.
Tabitha, you mind setting the table?
Okay, mom!
Really? You'reust gonna
throw that right there, huh?
Psst. Psst.
Daddy.
It's Marcos.
What? He kicked me off the mission.
He can't do that. Only I can do that.
You're back on the mission.
No need. I have my own mission now.
What could be more important
than my mission?
Gotta go. Lightspeed out.
This is so great.
Well, I hope you're hungry.
Been so long since I've used silverware.
So, how'd you like your first day?
Kind of intense.
Yeah. You'll get used to it.
Even that Nathan kid?
Nathan. Ugh. He's a mess.
Yeah. He's such a square.
- "A square"?
- Uh...
Yeah, you know, like a dork. Dweeb.
Nerdlet. A real Poindexter. Lame-o.
Dorkus to the Max...
They used to call me.
- You're weird.
- I am?
Yeah, but in a good way.
So, why is the pageant
stressing you out so much?
I have to sing.
- So what?
- I don't know.
My whole family is going to be there,
including my dad.
Oh. Right.
You're embarrassed of him?
No! No, it's not that.
It'sust, he's really good
at this kind of thing.
Being creative and using your imagination.
But it's hard for me.
Iust want him to be proud of me.
You know?
Really?
Well, yeah.
Um, who are these extra plates for?
Mom and dad.
Hey! The key still works.
You guys should really change the locks.
- Oh, you made it.
- Look who's here.
- Mom and dad.
- Grandma! Grandpa!
There she is!
Come here, my little tabby cat.
You're here!
Look at how big you are!
You're almost a teenager.
Can you vote yet?
- Ten and a half more years.
- Daddy, they're gonna recognize you.
No, no. It's fine.
I've got the glasses. See?
- Selfie!
- How do you do it again?
- Bring out the baby.
- Hide!
- Where are you hiding that baby?
-ust be cool. Be cool.
- There she is.
- Hello.
Hey, who's the new guy?
- That's Marcos.
- I gotcha!
Attention, babies.
Bienvenue. Willkommen.
Dobro pozhalovat' and namaste.
Uh, babies.
Hey, no more screen time.
Listen. Believe it or not,
I used to beust like you.
Yes. I even had parents.
Mine were child psychologists
- who made me part of an experiment.
- Really?
They exposed me to 10,000 hours of Mozart,
language lessons and public radio.
“Wow.
I hate public radio.
It was at that point I realized
I was smarter than my parents.
And with my first step,
I ran away from home.
Why? They pushed me around.
I got told what to do all the time.
But a single word changed my life.
"No."
- Say it.
- No!
Take a nap.
Nyet!
- Put on your coat.
- Nein/
eat your vegetables.
Nahi.
Are you gonna let grown-ups
push you around?
No! No! No, no, no!
- Are you?
- Good god, no!
That's right.
Why do parents get to be in charge anyway?
They had their chance,
and what did we get?
Pollution, politics, wars.
Ooh.
Not "ooh." Boo!
Boo!
The only thing holding us back is them,
but not anymore!
The moment that we've worked so hard for
is almost here.
- B-day!
- B-day?
B-day.
I'm this many.
No, it's not your birthday.
It's the beginning of the baby revolution.
Yay! And there'll be cake.
Cake for everybody.
B-day! B-day! B-day!
Cake! Cake! Cake!
No more rules.
Ooh 132 la.
- No more parents.
- Cake. Cake. Cake.
Uh-oh.
Pew, pew, pew!
Sayonara, mama and papal!
Oh, this is bad.
All right, pep rally's over.
Your parents are gonna pick you up.
This is my life's work.
Oh, yes, 17 long months.
To... no more parents.
Mmm.
Cheers to the revolution.
No. Nope. Nope.
- Oh, Tina.
- Oh, that's a keeper.
Oh, it's so cute. What's the app called?
It's called qtsnap.
- Oh! Show me how to download that.
- Everyone has it.
So, Marcos.
- Lightspeed? Is that what you said?
- Mm-hmm.
Sounds like a cartoon name.
It really does.
Well, my parents,
they're a little wacky, so...
Huh. It's like I know you
from somewhere.
- Uh, I don't think so.
- That is a keeper too.
Hey! Hey! Doesn't he look familiar?
I don't think I do.
Yeah, he looksust like Tim.
Yeah! You look like Tim!
Hmm?
Except Tim didn't wear glasses.
Ah, that's right. Tsk. Ah.
Huh. Well, how about that.
Hey, where is Tim anyway?
Tim and Ted are on a trip.
- Together?
- They're bonding.
Well, that's about time. Yeah.
Iust hope Tim's back in time
for the pageant.
Uh, why...
Why wouldn't he be there?
- Tim time.
- Tim time. Oh.
What's... what's Tim time?
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
Well, Marcos,
Tim time is like a black hole,
where things like reality
and being on time get lost.
Oh.
Tabitha's father
has a very active imagination.
Which is a good thing.
Yeah, that's...
I'd say that's a good thing.
Oh. Remember when he said
our boss was trying to kidnap us?
He did?
Or that his
baby brother could walk and talk,
but only when we weren't looking?
Wow. Turn around.
That's so dad.
You know, Ted was quite
a handful himself.
Oh, he could be very...
- Uptight.
- Mmm. Yes. High-strung.
Oh, remember the time he sued us?
Teenagers. Ugh.
He really looked up
to his big brother though.
- He did?
Oh, yeah.
He wouldn't leave him alone.
Everything Tim did, Teddy wanted to do.
Really? Yeah.
Tagalong-Teddy we called him.
- Well, not to his face.
- No, not to his face.
He was very litigious.
But you know what?
Your dad didn't mind.
He was so proud of his little brother.
- Oh, yeah.
- He loved showing him off.
Those guys did everything together.
They were best friends.
Just like you and me. Right, Tina?
Best friends forever.
Tickle monster!
That's so sweet.
- And this is my closet.
- Oh, cool closet.
And this is my bed, and this is my fish.
Hey! Wanna see something really cool?
Sure.
I made this vocalizer for Dr. Hawking.
- Hey, my old...
- What did you do?
Check this out.
Say hello, Dr. Hawking.
Hel...
Um...
He has performance anxiety.
Mmm. Yep.
Oh! This is lamb lamb.
Hey, lamb lamb.
That's my galaxy model
right up there on my shelf.
My scientist of the week award.
“Wow.
My geode rock collection and my telescope.
Sweet. Hey, cool guitar.
Yeah. That's my dad's.
Cool dad.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm a lot taller in my mind.
Hey, if you want,
I can help you with your song.
No! You can't.
Your ears will bleed.
Oh, please. It'll be fun.
How about this one? It's a classic.
Do we have to?
Come on, let's try.
Okay.
It's not gonna be good though.
Noudgment. We'reust having fun.
there's no place like home
for the holidays
please, stop.
No, stop. Ah...
no matter how far away you roam
good... try.
Ugh! Iust get so nervous.
That's okay.
Listen, all you gotta do is imagine
that you're inside the song.
Everything in the lyrics
is actually happening to you.
And you can see the notes.
»> well, if you want
to sing out, sing out
and if you want to be free, be free
» cause there's a million things fo be
wow. Whoa!
> You know that there are»
Marcos, wait up!
Come on.
and if you want to sing high
sing high
that's a little too high!
and if you want to sing low, sing low»
I got ya.
'cause there's a million ways fo go >
> you know that there are»
OMG, that's a lot.
aha, its easy»
aha, you only need fo try
you can sing what you want
yeah! This is fun!
the opportunity's yours»
whoo!
and if you do it your way
whoa.
you can do it today
Marcos, wait! Where are you?
Come on. You can do it.
I can't. I can't.
Now go for it.
Whoa.
Hey.
it's easy
you only need fo try >
all right. My turn.
Here we go. It's all you.
and if I want to sing out, sing out
yes, let it out.
> And if I want to be free, be free
'cause there's a million things fo be;
I know that there are
I know that there are >
I know that there are >»
=> you know that there are >
/ know that there are
wow. That was so great.
No, you were so great.
Thanks, Marcos.
Wha...
- Oh, that's a keeper.
- They can see us.
Guys, come on.
Stop. No, do it. Do it.
Oh, no.
Parents, right?
Bye, Templeton family!
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Marcos.
Lightspeed.
- Weird kid.
- Yeah, I don't like him.
catch my eye
take my hand
this bond is tighter than we...
you go get 'em, Tabitha.
...Ever planned >
give me courage
>so [can land >
pick up, pick up, pick up.
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
Choo-choo!
Don't they understand
it's the fate of the world?
I've been on hold forever!
All operators are currently napping.
I've been on hold so long
I got a tooth growing in.
Back in my day, we wrote memos.
That's cute and old-timey.
I weep for the future.
Do you wanna talk about your feelings now
while I'm on hold?
- I can give you 20 minutes.
- No.
Let's get to the nut. The nugget.
What are you afraid of?
Sharks.
Getting shot in the head with an arrow.
And the IRS. That's it.
There you go. Was that so hard?
Baby steps.
Now, what about being lonely?
- I'm not lonely.
- Mm-hmm.
I'must alone.
- There's a difference.
- I think it's time you read your file.
-ust give me.
- Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Whoa! This is it? It's so thin.
Dear boss baby, I promise you this:
Every morning when you wake up,
I will be there.
Every night at dinner, I will be there.
Every birthday party,
every Christmas morning, I will be there.
Year after year after year.
And you and I will always be brothers.
Always.
Makes me wanna make a sad face.
We wereust kids.
We didn't know anything
about the real world.
And eventually, you have to grow up.
Just because you grow up,
it doesn't mean you have to grow apart.
I don't know.
Maybe it's already too late.
Sorry I'm late.
Daddy! Daddy, daddy.
- What's going on?
- Uncle Ted really misses you.
Isn't that nice?
So, hey, uh, what you doing?
Oh, I was, uh... I don't know.
I wasust working on this.
Look, I'm sorry about
what I said at recess.
What happens on the playground
stays on the playground.
I was worried about Tabitha, you know?
She's your daughter. I get it.
This whole time, I was thinking about
what I wanted and not what she needed.
I think I finally got this parenting thing
figured out.
Gold star for you, daddy.
Keep it up, pops.
Well, about that, Armstrong wants to
get rid of parents somehow.
- Sorry, what?
- He's planning a baby revolution.
Ugh, come on!ust when I got good
at this whole parenting thing.
- We gotta stop him.
- Not we.
- You?
- Neither one of us.
- Babycorp is taking it from here.
- Ah.
They're gonna send in the baby seals
or something?
- Looks like it.
- So, you'll, um...
You'll be headed back to your office?
Uh, yeah.
Well, keep in touch, Tim.
Hello? Babycorp?
Thank goodness, babycorp.
Well, babyco... what?
What are you saying
there's not enough evidence, babycorp?
- Uh-oh.
- So, you're not gonna do anything?
But, babycorp... ugh!
Well, then we'll take care of it!
You know what, babycorp? I quit!
What a bunch of diaper sniffers. Well...
Looks like we have to stop Armstrong
ourselves.
We're going rogue.
I like it!
- So, the mission's back on?
- Yeah!
If you two can put up with each other
a little longer.
I suppose I can live with that. Tim?
I think that's doable.
Yay!
Forced together again!
It's 8:45 P.M.
Okay. Now our clock is ticking.
We have to stop Armstrong
before the formula wears off.
Working as a team,
we will strike at the pageant.
Go, Tina!
Now, this top-secret document...
- Sweeltie, it's the program.
- This top-secret program
reveals that Armstrong is scheduled
to address the audience,
which he will do right here,
at the very end.
We need someone backstage.
Tim, that's you.
How am I gonna get backstage
if I'm not in the pageant?
My people will take care of that.
Ah!
Thank you. Thank you.
- No!
- Great.
And... go!
Gluel
- no!
- There, there. All better.
Awesome!
Now, I'll be your eyes and your ears
in the audience.
I can't let mommy see me talk,
or she's gonna start squealing
and hugging me,
but these little doodads
will let you understand my baby talk.
It's called a gaga device.
- Hmm.
- Aw, that's cute.
Check it out.
- Can you hear me, daddy?
- Also cute.
Meanwhile, with my new purple status,
I can stay close to Armstrong.
Um, that's... that's an eyebrow.
- Oh. Sorry.
- Uh, no, that's, uh...
When the moment is right,
I'll implant a device.
- Got it.
- Got what?
I mean, you've got this.
Go get 'em, tiger.
Oh, thank you, parents. Thank you.
There's the old enthusiasm I like to see.
This will allow me fo control his suit.
I can make mutton chops do
whatever I want.
[ Can make him dance.
- I can make him prance.
- Hey, no!
Including exposing himself
fo the audience.
Every parent will pull out their phone.
Don't look at me. No!
The photos will spread like a diaper rash!
Cut to: Our pizza party.
Boom! Bam! Poo! Poof! Questions?
After Tabitha sings her solo, right?
After Tabitha sings.
Now weust sit back, relax
and enjoy the show.
Welcome, parents, fo our holiday pageant.
Remember, flash photography
in the auditorium is absolutely okay.
Take a picture.
Show your kids that you love em.
Yippee!
Come on, Tim.
You promised you'd be here.
Oh, sorry. This seat is taken.
- Yep. Sorry.
- Oh, no.
So sorry. Uh, sorry!
Sorry! I'm so sorry!
Uncle Teddy, are you in position?
The baby's in the cradle.
Papa bear, can you read me?
The flake has landed.
Places! Places, everybody.
- Here we go.
- Oh, my gosh!
- It's starting. It's starting.
- Finally.
It's starting. It's starting. Yay!
You're a big pageant guy, huh?
No, I'm not talking about the show.
I'm talking about b-day.
- B-day?
- Oh, yeah.
It's already in the parents' phones.
I taught babies to code.
Apps. They're writing apps.
But my next app...
Ooh, it's gonna change the world.
Forever.
Qtsnap is the app
that's going to change the world forever?
Forever starts today.
Uh, cool.
- it's wintertime >
- Christmas...
it's the best time of year
>... here d
but due fo ice caps melting
global warming's here
qd I feels like summer;
the snow has disappeared
it's all our parents' fault
9 so we're all doomed dal d
doomed!
This is kinda dark.
Did the kidsust say we're doomed?
What the heck are we watching?
Their brains are turning to mush.
Months of hypnotic research embedded
in the most user-friendly
photo app ever made.
Ooh!
Now all we need to do is sit back, relax
and enjoy the show.
- Hey!
- Right.
- I'll be right back. We're...
- and now we're going to tell you
- hey!
- Out of dundle floofers.
Mmm.
Diwali!
Las posadas!
Agnostic!
And hanukkah!
Your son is so talented.
Oh, so is yours.
Liars.
Tina, come in. B-day is happening now.
It's all in the phones.
Armstrong is using an app
to brainwash the parents.
Gasp!
We have fo stop the show.
Okay, there's a... there's a big old
no-touchy-switch backstage.
Daddy, we have to pull the plug!
Daddy, come in! Daddy, daddy, daddy!
Daddy, daadaly, daddy!
Ugh. He's not responding.
Of course not.
- I'll do it myself.
- Stop!
Theater kids only!
Oh, come on, nativity!
Look holier!
Hey, Tabitha.
Don't you worry, okay?
You're gonna be great.
Thanks, Marcos.
And thanks for all your help.
Anytime.
I feel like you really understand me.
I'm so excited.
I can't wait to see the look
on my dad's face when I sing.
Hey! You're on, Templeton.
Wish me luck.
And break a leg.
Or two, for that matter.
Psst.
- Tim!
- Is that the babyesus?
we have to shut down the pageant
- yeah!
- What? No, why?
Armstrong's turning the parents
into zombies
so they'll do whatever he wants.
What? What are you doing? No!
Tabitha's on next.
You'd risk the future of the world
to see your daughter sing?
Yes! I have to be there for her.
Look who's worried about
showing up for things all of a sudden.
What's that supposed to mean?
You didn't even come to my graduation.
- Ah! Which one?
- Business school.
Law school. None of them.
You didn't even come to my wedding!
- Which one?
- I only had one!
We had a deal, Tim.
You promised you'd be there always.
- Whoa.
- Breach of...
- Where did you...
- Contract!
- Whoa! Whoa!
- Whoal
how do you do there, fellas?
Nothing's gonna ruin my b-day.
Not even you.
Oh, busted.
It was obvious from the very beginning
that you two were working together.
What gave us away?
Well, I'd say the bickering,
the petty disputes, theealousy.
You know, you two are brothers
in every single way.
Off to the box they go.
What? No! Not the box.
Not now. Please.
Aw, it'sust too bad
that you're never gonna
have a chance to reboot your relationship
- and restore the closeness...
- No!
That you once felt.
- Sorry about that.
- No, no! No!
Adios, Marcos.
Oh! Look! Look! There she is.
There's our little angel.
- Tabby's in the tree.
- Ooh!
You had oneob to do.
Oneob.
- Oh, no.
- The fountain!
It's flooding the room!
This isn't a time-out.
It's game over.
Psst.
It's one, two, three, and one, two, three.
catch my eye
take my hand
> this bond is tighter
than we ever planned
give me courage
> so [can land >
> we know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand
laugh and cry with me
fly that high with me»
9 see the sunset and the sunrise»
wow.
the world looks so good
through our eyes
like the moon and stars at night
you're right.
I blew it. I ruined the mission.
And I'm a terrible father.
Hey, you did sort of ruin the mission.
But you're a great dad!
No, I'm not.
I could never do yourob.
I mean, you work around the clock.
You can't even quit if you wanted to,
and you don't even get paid.
Frankly, I don't see how that's legal.
I was alwaysealous of you.
I wanted to be successful too, you know.
Sure, Tim, I made a lot of money...
But you made a family.
The truth is...
It's lonely at the top.
> Reach with me
see the sky
I'll always be here
for the rest of your life
d> sail that ocean
> find that sand
> we know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand
You know, I'm... I'm sorry
we don't see each other anymore.
A very wise person once told me,
just because you grow up,
doesn't mean you have to grow apart.
- Was it Tina?
- Oh, yeah.
It is crazy how smart she is.
It's like she looks right into your soul.
I'm sorry that I missed your graduations.
I'm sorry I missed your one wedding.
I'm sorry I wasn't there for you.
side by side
> hand in hand
> we speak a language
no one else can understand >
hear those cheers
strike up the band
> we know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand
Oh, Tabitha.
Gramps? Nana? Mom?
Oh, no!
Oh, my gosh, Tabitha.
You did such a greatob.
Well, that'sust horribly rude
of you all.
Come on, everybody.
How about a standing ovation?
- Very good.
- They're zombies!
We did it!
The baby revolution has begun.
No more need for costumes.
Who wants cake?
Oh, my gosh!
Happy b-day, everybody.
Daddy, uncle Ted, come in.
Where are you?
Here you go, sis.
Now, I already used this,
so I know it's safe.
Thanks.
Wait. Are you talking?
I know. It's pretty weird, isn't it?
Oh, my gosh. You're talking!
It's an emergency.
I'm on a supersecret mission
from babycorp.
You mean dad's stories are true?
That's what the suit says.
How do I look?
No way!
Now, I can't get ahold of dad
or uncle Ted,
so I need your help, big sis.
Wait, wait, wait. Dad's here?
They've been here the whole time.
- Where?
- I don't have much time to explain,
but Dr. Armstrong is a baby.
A very bad, bad baby.
Soon, the world is gonna be
our playground.
Whee!
Now we can make parents
do whatever we want.
Awesome! Yeah!
No more rules.
Sayonara, mama and papa. Yeah!
- Mom?
- Dad?
Grandpa?
Whoa. Are you kidding me?
We need to shut it down
before it goes global.
- Yeah!
- What are we gonna do?
We need to find a big whatchamacallit
that controls the parents' phones.
- The server.
- Yes, yes!
Is there a big one of those whatsits
at school?
Uh, let's see.
Well, servers get really hot,
so you need air ducts...
Now you're thinking!
Which intersect at
the acorn!
A-plus!
Come on! This way.
Opportunity knocks.
First, we need to make a quick pit stop.
Your time has concluded.
It looks like this is it, Tim.
Well, hey,
at least we have these last final
precious moments together.
Precious.
Precious!
Oh, right.
Precious! Precious!
That's my girl.
Thank you...
Ah!
- Tina? Tina, come in, it's daddy.
- Daddy?
Listen, we have to shut down the server.
- It's in the acorn.
- Whoal
this is so weird.
I call shotgun!
- Quick, to the acorn!
- Hyanh!
Yee-haw!
Hold onto your chaps, pal.
Whoa!
Oh, no!
Glue!
Yah! Pixie dust!
Yeah, baby! Yes!
Wha...
Where'd I go?
- Whoal!
- I like your pajamas.
Where are you going?
- Hyah!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Glue!
- I'm proud to be a yellow.
I like your pony.
Thank you.
What?
Huh, huh, huh. No, no, no.
Now let's crack that big nut.
Oh, no! It's about to go worldwide.
How are we gonna get up there?
- Really?
- Well, you got grit.
I'll give ya that. Gumption, even.
Very admirable, and yet, annoying.
Quite annoying. Yeah.
I'm gonna have to, you know, stop you.
Glue me, glue me.
Precious, sic 'em!
You're too little and too late.
Ah! Bad... bad dog.
Pets aren't allowed in school.
Precious!
- And you, my pudgy protege...
- Go, go, go! Move!
I offered you the world.
We could have been partners!
I've got something better than a partner.
I have a brother.
Yeah!
- Let go.
- No, you let go.
Wow. Point taken.
What? What's going on?
Hey, that's my leisure suit.
It looks better on her.
Hands up, diapers down.
Things are about to get weird.
Yeah! That's my girls.
- That's really dad?
- Yep.
I said a lot of stuff to that kid.
Well, quite the family reunion.
Uh, the more the merrier.
- I say let's call your parents.
- Oh, no.
Uh-oh. Okay.
Mommy and daddy, let's hug 'em...
- To death.
- Don't worry about us. Get to the server.
Go, Tina, go! Whoo!
Uh... whoa!
- Hey!
- You got this, Tina.
Get down from there!
Go for his lollies!
Never touch another man's pony!
Here, stick around. Stick around.
Uh, Tim, what do we do now?
Don't move! Maybe they won't see us.
They see us, Tim. They see us!
- Did you move? I didn't move.
- Really, Tim?
- That's a little too high now.
- Don't look down.
- Look straight ahead, okay?
- Oh.
It's locked.
Can I give you a hand?
No, no, no!
- Hey! No! No!
- Thanks, sis.
Stay away from my server.
- Shut it down, Tabitha!
- What are you doing?
No, no! No! Don't do that.
- Oh, no!
- Hug grandpa.
- It's night of the living boomers.
- Hugs.
- Dad, stop!
- Hug.
Back! Back, you little monsters.
You back off, candy pants.
Got your nose!
Aw, right in the breadbasket!
- Knocked his block off!
- Ah, poopy.
Tina, I think I got it. Yes!
Don't hit that button.
And... enter.
No, no. Stop it. Cut it out.
Look what you made me do.
The fire alarm.
Ah! Darn it.
Dad! Uncle Ted!
Pull the fire alarm!
- The girls need help.
- No kissies!
The girls need us.
Time's up, halflings.
Great galloping gargoyles!
What? Where... what?
Tim! Get to the fire alarm!
I'll hold them back.
Make it rain, baby!
I'm on it. What's the matter?
You can't handle the awkward phase?
Go, Marcos!
Dad, go!
I'm back!
- Here we go!
- Come on.
How about another round, ya tough guy?
Come on!
Stop it!
I still got these.
You put my sister down!
B-day will happen,
whether you like it or not.
You shall not pass!
You shall not pass.
No! Stop passing.
Yeah, dad! Way to go! Whoo!
That's it?
That's right. Why, what?
The school's expensive.
I had to cut costs someplace.
- Oh, no. It's not working.
- Did you pull it right?
How else you gonna pull it?
You'll see I'm right. I'll show everybody.
The age of parents is over.
Yay, yay, yay.
Now, how about you watch me
have a little toast.
To the baby revolution, and to me.
It's time for the candy volcano...
Oh, that's good.
- Of doom!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing? No, no! No!
Oh, no, no, no!
- No, no!
- Boomshakalaka?
- Boom!
- Don't do that!
Whoa!
Oh, no! Tabitha.
No! Someone help me, please!
Tabitha. Hang on!
Ted, I need upsies. Now!
Dad, help me!
Look at you.
You're smart. You're strong.
You don't need parents.
What can they possibly offer you?
- How about unconditional love?
- Ah!
- That's what.
- No, no.
- Sayonaral!
- No!
Tabitha!
I'm gonna fall!
Tabitha! Hang on!
I gotcha! I gotcha!
Oh! I gotcha, Tabitha.
I gotcha.
That's my big brother.
Thanks, Marcos lightspeed.
I thought we both had to grow up.
Well, let's not grow up too fast.
I love you, dad.
I love you, Tabitha Templeton.
Aw.
You see that?
And you wanted to take it all away.
- Where you going?
- Home.
You know, doc,
childhood doesn't last forever.
But family sure does.
Uncle Ted, heads-up!
Whoo-hoo!
We win!
Get ready to order some pizzas.
Whoo-hoo!
Cool!
Huzzah!
Oh, sweet!
He who findeth, keepeth.
Mommy, daddy, I missed you so much!
Ooh, ooh, ooh. Yay!
Junior!
Gluel
so soft.
Where are we going?
Not bad, templetons.
Whoo-hoo! Yay, templetons!
Yeah, mission accomplished.
And as a bonus,
we stopped Armstrong too.
What?
My real mission
was getting you two back together.
A-plus! See me after class.
Wait, so you never actually quit?
- Nope!
- Huh!
Well played.
I don't like to mix the two,
but I will say, it was never business.
It was always personal.
You know what, kid?
You're the best boss I ever had.
Thank you, chief.
Tim! You actually made it.
- Yeah.
- I mean, I'd knew you'd make it.
- Teddy.
- Teddy, you're here.
- And look what you're wearing.
- Uh...
Sweetheart, I cried.
Then I went blank.
Oh, come on. Everybody get together.
We gotta get this. Here we go.
- Dad, no!
- No!
What?
> We know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand
> we know that divided we'll fall >
- yay, Tabitha!
- That was beautiful!
The crowd goes wild!
Thank you. Thank you.
Aw. Hey, precious.
You're amazing.
I wish Teddy could have been here.
Yeah, I know. Me too.
Hmm.
Hey, I wasust...
Merry Christmas, Tim.
I'm sorry I couldn't be there with you,
but please enjoy
this inappropriately lavish gift instead.
You've given me the greatest gift of all.
You.
Love, the best brother in the world.
P.s. Duck!
In your face, Leslie!
Hey! Oh, it is on, Lindsey!
- No, no. Don't!
- Come here!
Don't! I'm younger than you.
You're a bigger target!
- I got you so good!
- No, you didn't!
- You missed me!
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Ambush. Exactly.
- Ow!
- Sneak attack!
Isn't it great to see them fighting again?
Oh, finally.
Shouldn't you pick up?
Nah, we got some family business.
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Tina, we have another assignment for you.
I'm listening.
Grandma's coming in hot!
You want some of grandpa?
- Everyone, get tagalong-Teddy!
- Gotcha!
- /ts true.
- Not in the face!
- You can't stop time.
- It's cold!
But every once in a while,
you get a second chance.
- I'm gonna get you!
- So even though you're only a kid once...
- Okay, you got me!
- Well, unless you get to be a kid twice,
but the point is
you have to grow up sometime.
And you should always be nice
to your brother.
Ah, that was really sweel, daddy.
That'll be great for my report.
Okay. So, thats it then.
Well, actually,
there's one more little thing.
Mama?
- Papa?
- Wha...
My son!
Oh.
Oh, yes!
You came home!
Oh, yeah. Right.
Okay, pops. Now.
The end.
catch my eye
take my hand
> this bond is tighter
than we ever planned
give me courage
> so can land >
> we know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand
> climb with me >
share my dreams
tomorrow's brighter
than it's ever been”
fear no danger >
> make big plans
> we know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand
laugh and cry with me
fly that high with me»
jd see the sunset and the sunrise &»
the world looks so good
through our eyes
like the moon and stars at night
rest your head
tell me your thoughts
everything I haven't called mine
is all yours
d> sail that ocean
> find that sand
> we know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand
> Reach with me
see the sky
I'll always be here
for the rest of your life
side by side
> hand in hand
> we speak a language
no one else can understand >
jd hear those cheers,
strike up the band
> we know that divided we'll fall >
so together we stand